you stop?
Shut it up!
What in the world is going on?
How did Luffy's crew find us?
And Law is here as well.
I was told that he had been apprehended.
You were handing me this instant cardinal!
I beautifully reported everything
to Lord Orochi, just like always.
What could have gone awry?
It can't be.
Did Lord Orochi not arrange
any countermeasures for this?
Do you really think a regular old
bomb would take down a ship like ours?
Not a chance in hell, bro!
The Sunny can cross a thousand seas!
It's made of wood from the Tree of Adam!
It won't go down that easy!
You got anything else?
Cause those weak-ass
bombs ain't gonna cut it!
So the sabotage wasn't enough?
Those sneaky scumbags couldn't
put a scratch on our ship.
The sails are another story, though.
Sorry we're late, Keen Aemon.
We had to patch up the sails,
and that took a little while.
Quite all right, though
it gave me a scare.
Hey, Keen!
Where is everybody?
I thought you were bringing backup.
I guess our original plans
kind of changed, huh?
Is it okay if we smash those
battleships to pieces then?
Yes, what happened?
I was under the impression we would
have lots of reinforcements here.
Yeah!
Where's 3,500 people from the labor camp?
Indeed, what's the status?
Where are the Yakuza, who are supposed
to be coming from all over the country?
Weren't there about 200 or so of them?
Something's not adding up.
Dogstorm had 200
musketeers at Hitachi Port,
and then the Atomiyama
Thieves Brigade had 280.
Yeah, and where are all
the ships we repaired?
There were dozens of them.
What happened?
And what about that supply of swords and
spears that was coming in from Ringo?
Without weapons for our
troops, we're screwed.
Hey, Kin'emon!
Know anything about this?
I confess, a substantial misstep was made.
My deepest apologies, Sir Luffy.
Regrettably, the entire plan was leaked.
I wish I could tell you where the
others are, but I know nothing at all.
So that's the reason why nobody's here.
We should think about retreating, maybe.
No way!
That's messed up!
We don't know jack about what's going on.
In fact, we thought we sunk your
ship until just a second ago.
But we did sink all of
the ships at the dock.
You should have seen the port last night.
The Shogun was thorough.
He had us bombed the major bridges, too.
Now there's no passage
between the regions.
You get it, right?
There's not a chance in hell
anyone's coming to help you!
Even if they made it to the poor,
no one's going to be reaching
Onigashima without a boat!
And this was your last chance, the
only day the raid might succeed!
And by the way,
I heard we're going to start killing
all the rebels we rounded up tomorrow!
I almost forgot.
There's one last thing
we need to tell you.
Sorry about that.
Figured there's only so
much bad news you can take.
Bad news, you say?
That banquet we're having isn't
just for the Fire Festival.
It's much bigger than that.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
celebration because the Beast
Pirates and the Big Mom Pirates
are forming the ultimate alliance!
You have got to be shitting me!
Two emperors teaming up?
We're unstoppable with both Commander
Daddy and Big Mom on our side.
No matter who you recruit,
you got nothing on us!
The worst generation?
Yeah, I'll say.
Sink him and get this over with already!
Now get ready to fire!
Meh, you're really full
of yourselves, huh?
Well, I'm sick of it!
Stand back, you guys!
You stand back.
Take your own dumb advice.
I got this, Drop!
Make yourself useful and stay out of it!
I said no, back off!
All right, ladies, stop your bickering.
I got this.
Hey, Jaggy, not you, too!
I doubt you're annoying!
Neither of you better
get in my way! Watch me!
I was here to watch!
Get back here!
I said I got that!
Oh, like hell, you do!
You back off! No way!
Room's even more effective in the rain.
No fair!
Your power's too cool!
Why do you gotta go and rub it in?
Suck it up.
You don't need to be a damn Chef!
Oh, the kettle has an opinion.
You're both dumb!
I can wrap this up in one shot, you know!
Once you shut up, I'll show I can do the
same damn thing in half the time as you!
We're wasting time.
I'm going in and you can't stop me.
You got that, losers?
Losers!
Now I'll kick your ass first!
Good, because I'll handle these guys!
You're ridiculous.
Hey, you three!
Don't go thinking that
you'll leave here alive!
Shut up!
You're beneath me!
You shut up.
I'll take care of him. Oh, yeah?
It's on now!
Rude!
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
That's me!
Ah!
Nice!
Injection shot!
See what I did there?
Who's the loser now, loser?
Let me make one thing perfectly clear.
I'm the one who sank that last ship.
I sank that thing, it was all me!
Get out of here with that!
You're taking credit for my work!
Wait, aren't those three
guys in an alliance?
Up ahead!
That's the Kyoshiro family ship!
Perfect timing, Kyoshiro!
We had nothing to fear!
Seems you're in quite a bit of trouble!
We could really use some help!
The Shogun ordered for them to be
sunk to the bottom of the sea, bud!
You don't say.
Orders to sink the enemy, huh?
Allow me.
Boss!
There's something you're not telling us!
I have no desire to sink you, so
I simply disabled the cannons!
you had aimed at the samurai's vessel.
I know him.
We fought before.
Careful with this one!
He's terrifying with a blade!
This man is one of the Shogun's lapdogs.
He's the Yakuza boss who
took over after Yoguro.
Greetings to you, Akazaya Samurai.
I'm the reputable gangster
who runs the Flower Capital.
The people there know
me as Napping Kyoshiro.
My family's made up of 200 men.
Our swords are at your
disposal for the raid.
They're doing what now?
Are you joking, boss?
Explain yourself!
What favor do you owe us?
Do you not operate under Orochi?
My intent is to pay back the immeasurable
debt that I owe the Kozuki clan.
You have been in my
thoughts, King, for years.
You know me?
Do you recall when the Mountain God
charged into the capital 40 years ago?
The public believed that
the chaos was the result
of Lord Odin's antics But
they were wrong in that
assumption It was in fact
caused by you and your
ill-advised plan to get
rich by selling a young boar
What?
But only one man knows
about what happened that day
Why do you think everyone
calls it the mountain god?
What?
It's all my fault.
The capital's doomed and it's my fault.
No, don't tell me.
Is that you, Digital? You
can't be. It's really true?
It is I.
I suppose you wouldn't recognize me.
I wish to join you right away.
However, I determined it'd be
wiser to appear to be your enemy.
Just a bit longer.
Imagine if I revealed who I was.
The betrayer in your midst would have
relayed that to Orochi and had me killed.
Denjiro!
Silence, you!
Instead, I retained his
trust until the end,
and I liberated the 1,000 samurai
locked in the Rasetsu prison quarters.
There are more ships?
Enemy reinforcements.
You can add 1,200 soldiers to the total.
We've been waiting for this day, and
we're ready to fight with all we've got!
Since when has boss killed Shura
one of the damned Akazaya Samurai?
Going for Morigashima before
it's too late! Yes, sir!
It's really you!
Commendable work, Keen.
I knew you were sharp,
but I must hand it to you.
You understood Lord Yasui's
message and adapted quickly.
Two birds of flame to represent time.
A Habu Viper to indicate location.
And a reversed crescent moon,
which signifies rebellion.
Twilight, the second hour of
the Bird at Fire Festival.
It shall take place at Habu Port.
The initial symbol did
not have those two lines.
That was the one that
Orochi got his hands on.
Before his death, Lord Yasui
altered it and helped get word out.
Obviously, the newly added lines
going through the serpent's stomachs.
instruct the reader to remove
the midsection of the word.
So without the letters in the center,
Habu Port, also called Habu Monda,
becomes Head!
It means wharf.
Lord Yasui always did love the view
of the maple tree forest from there.
Huh?
Even though it was a simple message,
you deliberately misinterpreted
it when you spoke!
Sensing there was a
spy amongst your group,
you pretended to direct
your associates elsewhere!
But you knew they were wise
enough to discern the truth!
At any rate, the point is,
each of these ports is associated
with a particular animal.
With the moment's consideration, the image
of a lizard will likely come to mind.
Thus, Tokage Port in Udon.
Thinking back, that symbol
never did look like a lizard.
I had no reason to question it
because Master Keen was so confident.
The unwitting spy passed a long word at
the false rendezvous point to Orochi.
Just as you planned, Master Keen.
Such is the foolishness of a man
who did as he pleased for too long.
Orochi misjudged the distance between
locations and waited until last night to act!
By the time they began their assault,
all of your allied forces had
already crossed the bridges,
and the ships you needed
had left the port!
The ones they sank were
those few left behind.
So according to your plan, the
4,200 troops concealed themselves.
They laid in wait within the Maple
Forest near the wharf at Habu Port.
You mean they're still alive?
It may be 20 years later, but I still
remember Lord Odin's legendary death.
We've lived every day believing
the Kozuki clan would return.
Hakusaya 9, let us fight together.
We are here to aid you.
The plan to raid Onigashima
hasn't missed a single step.
Combine our 1,200 soldiers with your
troops and you now stand at 5,400 strong!
Onward to the banquet!
Would you look at that!
I don't really follow what happened,
but it looks like everything worked out.
There's too many of them!
Things aren't looking good for us!
Any news from Onigashima?
Can't get a hold of them!
I bet they're preoccupied
with the big party right now!
So my efforts were all
for naught in the end!
Damn you, Kin'emon!
Bravo!
As expected,
you have risen to the occasion and
proven to be quite the capable leader!
Yes, Worf, of course.
Not Tokage Port.
You, Gar, can be honest with
us, Kin'emon. No offense,
but we've known you long enough to know
that a plan like this is not within
your skill set just admit you made a
mistake and we won't be angry stop it.
You thought the message was
tokage you cannot fool me.
I said stop it at least
the mistake settled in
our favor what a happy
accident to be honest.
I fear that i might perish
in the battle ahead.
I did just use up a whole lifetime's
worth of luck after all i can scarcely.
I disagree with that.
Master Kin'emon!
We'll follow you anywhere!
Though if you are lucky, then we are lucky
to have you at our side in this battle.
And even if you do die out there, at the
very least we will all die beside you.
We serve Lord Odin together
and will avenge him together.
We may have come from different worlds,
but we are comrades in arms now.
To the end.
Such pleasantries from scoundrels
like you hardly comforting.
Hold up your sword with pride, keen!
We shall claim victory
in the opening fight.
Win or lose, I'm prepared.
We will avenge Lord Odin; the time is now!
You have our full support,
no matter the cost!
Never mind, Kin'emon.
I must make haste to Onigashima.
The role assigned to be by Lord
Orochi is still unfulfilled.
There's one thing I have left to do.
Anjirou, you won't take Lord Momonosuke!
What will that do?
I am on my way! Stop it!
You'll drown if you jump into the sea!
You would trample our dreams
and get us with a smile!
You bastard!
I admit, I do find
pleasure in this moment.
Sabotage, duplicity, betrayal
with a surprise ending.
What a complex role I
had the honor to play.
And speaking of roles, thank you
all so much for playing the fool.
KONTINO!
What better way to end the play than
to stain the stage with Kozuki blood?
Kawamatsu, help!
Lord Momonosuke!
Don't you worry, Momonosuke.
I'll let your sister
follow you into death.
You hear that, Kawamatsu?
I will find Hiyori and slay her, too.
You fools confirm she's alive after all.
Damn you, Kanjuro!
That crane you painted
is flying immaculately!
What of the monstrosities you made us?
They washed away with water!
I thought you lacked talent! Huh?
It's too high!
Someone please get me
down from here, please!
I don't want to die! Kanjuro? Momo?
Wait, where are you going?
This is the last you'll ever see of me!
This is only a fraction
of Commander Taito's army.
You'll be dead before
you ever reach the shore.
Someone help me!
Let him go!
Lord Momonosuke, no!
You'll pay for betraying
the Akazaya 9, Kanjuro!
Stay strong, Lord Momonosuke!
This is terrible!
Damn.
So the whole plan nearly
fell apart because
Kanjuro's been feeding info to the enemy?
So it would seem.
We better save Momo quick.
On it.
Hey, Reef!
It turns out Kanjuro is
actually an enemy spy!
He's taking Momo away right now! Huh?
Are you sure?
No way!
He fooled us all this time
and nobody had a clue!
What a jerk!
We can't let that bastard get away!
I'll try to shoot him down!
Special attack!
Green Star Platinus!
Shoot him in!
A valiant effort, but not enough!
I don't have time to
entertain imbeciles like you!
What's that cloud?
I have a bad feeling
about this, Sir Sanji.
Turn back immediately.
Clouds, clouds.
Whatever technique he's doing,
I've never seen it before.
Ink clouds.
Ink arrows.
Fall like rain.
Ukiyo Portrait, evening shower.
It's dangerous here!
Turn the boat around quickly!
I need help! Nami!
only one man's allowed
to shoot an arrow through
nami and robin's heart
figuratively and that man is me
i am begging you to
please stop this Kanjuro
you are going to kill
every last one of them
that i shall and rightfully
so it's their time
Your father, Rodin,
and your mother, Toki,
dangled a false hope
in front of those poor
fools by delaying their inevitable deaths.
Now, twenty years later, their
execution must be completed at last.
Frankly,
it would be a mercy since
those foolish samurai are
now serving under a cowardly
little imp like yourself.
You are nothing but an
imprudent child lacking in
conviction and whimpering
at the first sign of danger.
You can cry but I will laugh!
What am I to say?
I know best of all that I'm no Kozuki Onion
For how can I ever hope to measure up?
What am I supposed to do? I'm helpless!
Are you certain that's
what you want to say?
If you tell them that, no
one will come to your aid.
But...
Everyone!
Can you hear me?
That's Lord Momonosuke
I ask you that you do not
worry about my well-being
That is exactly what the
enemy wants you to do
I promise to you,
I shall escape all on my own You
must defeat Conney and Orochi
without me Please find a way
to protect the land of Moro
Such noble words from the
young lord It stirs my
heart to hear them How brave
you've turned out to be
We all put our faith in you That
was pretty manly Nice job, Momo
Hey, Momo
It's okay, I know
You're just a little
crybaby with a dumb Totknot!
What are you gonna do anyway?
Nothing, and you know it too!
How could you be so rude to him?
You better take that back!
Who's this guy anyway?
I'll chop him up!
Gotta find a way to survive, okay?
Just hang on, and we'll come rescue you!
Because you're my friend.
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Okay!
Off to Onigashima! Yeah!
Luffy!
One of the enemy's ships is getting away!
Just let it go!
They're all heading in
the same direction anyway.
We can sink them later.
Huh?
Hey, wasn't there another ship?
There was.
Then I sunk it.
Master King, forgive me.
I failed to protect him.
You are alive.
Then that's enough.
I doubt they will take Ward
Momonosuke's life right away.
One question, though.
Your face!
How did it transform so?
A tale for another time.
It is good to see you.
Is everyone all right?
Who needs help?
We have a few injuries and
some ships in need of repair.
I appreciate it, but I'll
just head for the island.
I didn't come this far just to die at sea.
Hey, my ship is not your
personal samurai garrison.
I said you're not welcome
here pack it up then make
sure the Straw Hats don't
hog all the glory Yeah!
What was that?
Oh, he's firing!
It's the ship that got away!
On-range cannon?
They can still hit us from
all the way over there!
So they weren't running away,
they were just repositioning!
These are our high precision cannons.
The best in Wano.
We got weapons factories all over the
country pumping these bad boys out.
And if these don't do the job, we have
plenty of other ways to blow you up!
Why don't you come at us?
Show us what you got.
Are you scared?
Hold the ship back!
Those shots can save us from here!
Damn it.
I thought it was weird that
they fled without a fight.
Full speed ahead!
We gotta get closer!
I don't care how many samurai ships
sink as long as we make it there.
Damn it.
We can't let them keep this distance.
We'll sink.
We must close the gap.
Seems this battle's already over.
We're untouchable from back here!
Now fire! Fire!
Fishman Caracal!
Spill it away!
Oh, crap!
There's a huge hole in the ship!
It's falling!
Fishback karate!
Spear wave for a summer!
That guy just destroyed
all of our cannons!
Something is happening over there.
What if a child drowned at sea?
And came back as a vengeful ghost!
intent on killing them all?
No!
You got the vengeful part right.
Wait, but what was that?
I think somebody's down there.
Everyone, if I may have a word.
I hail from the Fishman
District of the Ryugu Kingdom.
A place beneath the waves for
those bold enough to seek passage.
My apologies for the trouble
I may have caused you,
especially seeing that I'm a new recruit.
But I have ventured here
today to share a ceremonial
cup of sake with the boss of
the Straw Hat Pirate Crew.
If you'll have me, that is.
I'm known as
First son of the sea, Jinbei
Are you kidding?
He is seriously going
to join the Straw Huts.
It hasn't been long.
So I'm certain you'll remember me!
Now let's make this official, shall we?
Ah!
Jinbei!
It's Jinbei!
So sorry to keep you waiting,
but I thank you for indulging me.
Luffy, I have come back
alive just as I promised.
Glad I made it back in
time for the big battle.
We'll be back.